Soutar, Douglas H. Papers 5914
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Blue Ribbon Committee (Labor Law Study Group & old Blue Ribbon Committee). (Box 8)
  - LLRS/ LLSG- Policy Committee (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - LLSG- Fortune Article 2/71, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - LLRS/ LLSG - Labor Law Reform Study, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Greenspan Letter, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - LLRS/LLSG - Blue Ribbon Committee of Lawyers for Labor Law Reform, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - LMC-more recent- general (Folder 1 of 4), 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - LMC-more recent- general (Folder 2 of 4), 1976-1983 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - LMC-more recent- general (Folder 3 of 4), 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - LMC-more recent- general (Folder 4 of 4), 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - LMC- more recent- meetings, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - The Business Roundtable Labor Management Committee 1982 Annual Meeting (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - BR- Labor/ Management Committee- Objectives, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - BR- LMC "More Recent" General, 1964-1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Blue Ribbon Committee (small amount; more recent re Business Roundtable; Labor-Mgt. Committee). (Box 9)
  - BR- Public Info Committee, 1970-1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Study of U.S. Economic Knowledge and Attitudes Toward Business Conducted for the Public Information Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - BR PI Comm.+ LMC "More Recent", 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - BR- Public Info Comm., 1973-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - BR- Executive Committee Meetings 1972, 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Relations Department Legislative and Regulatory Update, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Br- Labor/ Management Committee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - BR- Labor Management Committee- Economic Research Comm., 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - BR- Public Information Comm. Reisel Column, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - BR- Public Information Comm. General 1970-1977 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - BR- Public Information Comm. General 1970-1977 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - BR- Public Information Comm. Meetings 1972-1975, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - BR Labor- Management Committee- Public Relations Subcommittee, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - BR- Public Information Comm. Meetings, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Comparable Worth Literature, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Business Roundtable Employee Relations Committee Meeting, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - BR- Appts., 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - The Business Roundtable Employee Relations Committee 1983 Annual Meeting (Box 9, Folder 18)
    D.H. Soutar (Meeting Notes Inside)
  - The Business Roundtable Employee Relations Committee 1984 Annual Meeting (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - BR PI Committee (Folder 1 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - BR PI Committee (Folder 2 of 7) The California Roundtable, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - BR PI Committee (Folder 3 of 7), 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - BR PI Committee (Folder 4 of 7), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - BR PI Committee (Folder 5 of 7), 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - BR PI Committee (Folder 6 of 7) PI Committee Meeting January 28, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - BR PI Committee (Folder 7 of 7) PIC Meeting 3/18/81, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Reference Manual For Continuing Legal Education Program, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - BR- LMC- Pension Task Force, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - BR LMC (Folder 1 of 5), 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Labor-Management Committee (later period)). (Box 10)
  - BR LMC (Folder 2 of 5), 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - BR LMC (Folder 3 of 5), 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - BR LMC (Folder 4 of 5), 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - BR LMC (Folder 5 of 5), 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - BR - Labor/ Management Committee Meetings 1972-1974 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - BR Labor Management Committee Meetings 1972-1974 (Folder 2 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - BR - Labor/ Management Comm.- DS 12/2/74 Letter, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - BR Labor-Management Committee- Subcommittee on OSHA, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - BR- Labor-Management Com. National Health TF- Washington Business Group on Health, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Business Roundtable- Airlines Mutual Aid Agreement, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - BR- LMC- National Health Insurance Task Force, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - BR LMC- Productivity Task Force 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - BR- Labor/ Management Committee Meetings 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - BR Labor Management Committee Meetings 1975-1976 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - BR- Labor Management Committee Landrum- Griffin Act., 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - BR- Labor Management Comm. Workers Compensation Subcommittee, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - BR- Labor Relations in the Public Sector and Public Employee Labor Relations Sector, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - BR- Welfare for Strikers, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - BR- "Food Stamps for Strikers", 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - BR- Labor- Management Committee - Subcommittee on Membership, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - BR- Labor- Management Committee- Industrial Relations Reps, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - BR LMC Meeting, 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - The Business Roundtable Labor-Management Committee Meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Business Roundtable Agenda Labor-Management Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - BR- Executive Committee General, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Appointments early 1970's & later into 1980's (Some appointments later Reagan period). (Box 11)
  - BR - Liaison Committee General, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - BR- Liaison Committee Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - BR Pol Com Meets + Liaison Comm. General, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - BR - Policy Committee Meetings 1973-976, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - BR Policy Committee Meetings 1973-1976 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - BR - Policy Committee- Meetings- 1977-78, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Br- LLSG- Hill & Knowlton (Folder 1 of 2), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Br- LLSG- Hill & Knowlton (Folder 2 of 2), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - BR- Labor/ Management Comm. General 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - BR - National Commission for Industrial Peace.., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - BR - Labor Management Comm. MNC- ILO Task Force, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - BR - Labor-Management Committee- Privacy Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - BR- Labor Management Comm. General 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - BR- Labor/Management Comm. General 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - BR - Policy Committee General, 1969-1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - BR- LMC- Productivity Task Force 1973-1975 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - BR- LMC- Productivity Task Force 1973-1975 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Labor Law Reform Study, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - BR- Policy Committee Employment & Balanced Growth Act a/k/a Humphrey-Hawkins Bill, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - TT- Issues, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - TT 2 For Schub - Kilb MTB (Folder 1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - TT 2 For Schub - Kilb MTB (Folder 2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Some early Stuff (Some on Browne; some later re Ed Miller & Lubbers; appointments 1970-1980's). (Box 12)
  - LMC Report BR Annual Meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Board Member + G.C. 1975 (Walther + Irving) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Walther + Irving (1973), 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1975- GC and BM Unavailable or Eliminated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Board Member 1977 (Truesdale) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 11-15-90 Reviewed General history appts 1968 to 70's, Cabinet level on down egshultz Duc (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 11-15-90 Reviewed General history appts 1968 to 70's, Cabinet level on down egshultz Duc (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Transition T, 1968-1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Transition (Folder 1 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Transition (Folder 2 of 3), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Transition (Folder 3 of 3), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - NLRB 1971-GC, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Appts late 60's, + 70's (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - NLRB 2, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - OSHA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 3/13/84 NLRB et al, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - APPTS WH 12-82, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - American Smelting and Refining Company + Burkhardt #1, 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - NLRB # 2, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Appointments (General). (Box 13)
  - OSHA-MSH, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Appointments- US, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - John L. Harmer+ Memorandum for Mr. D.H. Soutar, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - NLRB 80-81, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1975 B.M. + G.C., 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Betty Murphy, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - NLRB - Lubbers' Hearing, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bd. Chairman 1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Current Developments+ Appointments FMCS, 1969-1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - NLRB, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Labor Attorneys- Rankings for J. Hodgson, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - NLRB, 1970-1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - NLRB 1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Loose Mat 1968 + Miller Appointments, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - NLRB, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    "Betsy" Lisbeth Godley 456-2824
  - Daniel Pollitt, 1958-1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Ed Miller (Folder 1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ed Miller (Folder 2 of 2), 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Lawyers List NLRB, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Appointments, 1966-1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - NLRB 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Soutar Speeches. (Box 14)
  - Appointments-Assorted (Folder 1 of 4), 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Appointments- Assorted (Folder 2 of 4), 1969-1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Appointments- Assorted (Folder 3 of 4), 1959-1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Appointments-Assorted (Folder4 of 4), 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Truesdale 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - File Memorandums, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Pope, Ballard, Shepard & Fowle+ ASARCO Incorporated, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Appointments Assorted (Folder 1 of 5), 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Appointments- Assorted (Folder 2 of 5), 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Appointments - Assorted (Folder 3 of 5) Betty Murphy, 1970-1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Appointments- Assorted (Folder 4 of 5), 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Appointments- Assorted (Folder 5 of 5), 1974-1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Judy L. Waldman EEO + NLRB, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - United States of America Before the National Labor Relations Board Division of Judges, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Current Developments + Confirmed Appointments, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - NLRB- Daily Labor News, 1976-1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Appts 83, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Appointments- Assorted (Folder 1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Appointments- Assorted (Folder 2 of 2), 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Soutar Speeches (Copper Strike file 1968). (Box 15)
  - NAM December 6, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - FMCS Washington, D.C. November 16-20, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - FMCS January 10, 1965 New Orleans, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - IRRA February 18, 1965 N.Y.U. Faculty Club (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Columbia U. Group February 24, 1965 Men's Faculty Club (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - DS Speech Spring Meeting 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Hygiene FDN. 10/20/65, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - DS- N.Y. State Self- Insurers December 9, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - NAM October 20, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Hygiene Foundation October 21, 1964 Pittsburgh, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Panel Discussion Las Vegas 4-24-54, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - San Francisco Feb. 1956 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Las Vegas March 20, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Management, Club of P.A. April 26, 1962 Perth Amboy YMCA (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Conference on Aging- U. of Michigan June 15, 1962 Ann Arbor (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Industrial Relations Counselors Oct. 10, 1962 Key Biscayne (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - American Management Association March 11, 1959 New York (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Wayne State University May 3, 1957 Detroit (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - N.Y.U. Labor Conference June 12, '57 New York, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Slichter Seminar Oct. 2, 1957 Harvard (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - American Management Association Oct. 14, 1957 New York (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - American Management Association Feb. 18, 1958 Chicago, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Spring Meeting March 18,1957 San Francisco (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Workmen's Compensation D.S. Talk I.H.F. 10/58, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Industrial Relations Counselors November 12, 1962 Williamsburg (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - MT. States Employers Council Jan. 29, 1963 Denver (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - National Metal Trades April 12, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Spring Meeting - S.F. March 19, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Industrial Hygiene Foundation October 25, 1961 Pittsburgh (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - N.Y. St. School of Ind. And Labor Relations Feb. 14, 1961 New York, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - N.Y. St. School of Ind. And Labor Relation. May 3, 1960 New York (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - National Electrical Manufacturers Assoc. April 16, 1959 New York (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Y.M.C.A. May 20, 1959 Jersey City (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Industrial Relations Institute- Navy Dept. Nov. 1, 1963 Washington (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - National Metal Trades Association Sept. 24, 1963 New York (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Interim Report To National Affairs Section from Bonner Bill Subcommittee August 7, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Soutar Speeches. (Box 16)
  - National Metal Trades April 22, 1963 New York (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Spring Meeting Las Vegas 4-2-63, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Shulman Conference March 9, 1963 Yale (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "The Copper Strike" NAM Article, June 1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Spring Meeting - Las Vegas 6/3/68, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Managers' Meeting, 1967-1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Copper Strike's Meaning to Industry, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - NAM Reports 6-17-68 (Folder 1 of 3), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - NAM Reports 6-17-68 (Folder 2 of 3), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NAM Reports 6-17-68 (Folder 3 of 3), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Waldorf- Astoria, N.Y. Collective Bargaining Forum May '69, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Process Equipment Manufacturers Assn. Chicago May 21, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - DS Speech Spider 10/18/73 Reston, Virginia, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Hygiene Foundation Speech October 11, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - MIT Speech November 15, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - DS Speech O' Hare Inn 11/20/72, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - IRRA- Toronto Speech December 1972 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - DS Speech IRRA - Philadelphia 1-9-73 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - DS Speech IRA- St. Louis 1-17-73, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - D.S. Speech AMA - 2-21-73, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - DS Speech IMDI 3/13/73 What Business can Expect, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - D.S. Speech Conference Board 3-20-73, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - DS Speech Washington D.C. 3/20/73 Conference for Corporate Executive, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - D.S. Speech ACF Industries Brookings Institute 3-22-73, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - American Iron & Steel Institute May 21, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - DS Speech London, England IIRA 9/3/73, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - DS Speech Ripon Conference Washington D.C. 12/1/73, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - DS Speech University of Iowa 10/25/73 Iowa City, Iowa "Industrial Relations in the '70s", 1970 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - DS Speech Iowa Chapter IRRA 10/24/73 Ames, Iowa, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Aggravation of Chronic Diseases in Industry, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - American Trucking Assoc. DS Speech- July 18,1967 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - NAM Hot Springs September 11, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - NAM October 11, 167, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - NAM Industrial Relations Clinic Philadelphia- November 8, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    2 tabs on folder- November 9 - East Orange, N.J.
  - Arkansas State Chamber of Commerce Little Rock November 15, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Humble Oil Galveston November 15, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - November 28, 1967 Labor Relations Council - Phila., Pa. (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Balt., Md. 12/7/67 Industrial Relations Council, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - AMA Palmer House Chicago Feb. 14, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - NAM - Industrial Relation. Panel Feb. 29,1988 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - National Petroleum Refiners Assn. April 24, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Denver - Jan. 24, 1967 DS- MT. States Employers Council, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Soutar Speeches. (Box 17)
  - DS- American Management Assoc. 2/6/67 NY, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - DS Speech- Hawaii March 13, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - IRRA - December 29-30, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Relations Conference Berkeley- May 27, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Advanced Management Research Washington, D.C. - June 11, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining. In the 1970's Chicago - August 27, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kansas City IRRA October 15, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - "DS - AMM Interview - 4/3/70", 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - N.Y. Chamber of Commerce - Taylor Law Forum - June 13, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - DS Article for Modern Manufacturing (Factory) July 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - American Mining Congress Oct. 1968 Las Vegas (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Communication Council October 15, 1968 NYC (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - St. Bonaventure University Allegany, N.Y. November 16,1968 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Manager's Meeting 1969 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Conference Board "Survey of Business Opinion & Experience" 1972 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Conference of National Organizations- Miami, Beach 11/5/70, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Westchester Accountants Assoc. April 20, 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce November 10, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - U. of Pa., Wharton School November 18, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - M.I.T. December 1, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Association of the Bar of City of NY December 8, 1971, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - IHF- 34th Annual Meeting October 15, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - IRRA New Orleans December 27, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Annual Copper Development Assoc. Ind. Relation. Symposium 9/26/69, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - White House Conference on Industrial World Ahead Feb. 7-9, 1972 (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - White House Conference on Industrial World Ahead Feb. 7-9, 1972 (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - White House Conference on Industrial World Ahead Feb. 7-9, 1972 (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Secretary Hodgson's Meeting February 10, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - DS Speech University of Wisconsin Sem. Meth. Disp. Stlmnt 4/24/73, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - DS Speech MCA Cherry Hill N.J. 5/9/73, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - DS Speech New York Chapter IRRA New York 5/17/73, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Madison March 15, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - American Mining Congress Palm Springs. California march 21, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Pace College New York April 7, 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - N.Y. University May 26, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Notre Dame June 9, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Dept. of Labor Disc. Re IR research Program 6/24/72, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - IRRA Speech Kalamazoo October 2, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Construction Users Anti- Inflation Roundtable November 14-16, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - A Forward Look at Labor Management Relations Within the Framework of a Free Enterprise System (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Soutar Speeches. (Box 18)
  - A Forward Look at Labor Management Relations Within the Framework of a Free Enterprise System (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Co Determination, Industrial Democracy and the Role of Management (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 10/19/76 Pace University "The State of the Economy and Collective Bargaining", 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 9/16/76 Wash. D.C.: "President's Commission on Personnel Interchange", 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 11/16/76 NYPMA "The Pros & Cons of Salaried Status for all employees", 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Shultz Speech - AMC 9-14-77, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - William K. Zinke 2/8/78 Influence of European Work Practices on American ATT. & HAB., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Nonferrous Bargaining Structures- Unions & Companies", 1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - NYC's Annual Briefing Session on Coll. Bargaining. - NYCCI - 3-7-77 - DS'S Intro. Remarks, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration at the Cross- Road by Harry T. Edwards 4/19/77 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Donald H. Wollett 5/13/77 Benjamin Whitaker Memorial Symp., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Talk at Industrial College of The Armed Forces - 2/1/77, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Pace University - 5 Minute Presentation- Awards Luncheon 3/15/77, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - IRRA 1977 Annual Meeting "The Management View", 3/17/77 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - DS Speech IRRA Meeting New York December 28, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Montreal Speech-- May 25, 1976 "Labor and the Multinationals" (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Montreal Speech-- May 25, 1976 "Labor and the Multinationals" (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Montreal Speech-- May 25, 1976 "Labor and the Multinationals" (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Health Foundation, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Executive Enterprises Inc. 1974 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Albany - IRRA February 19, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Romney Meeting, Wigwam, Arizona March 20, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - FMCS, Western Conference Las Vegas, March 20, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Hawaii Employers Council Mauna Kea, Hawaii April 6, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - DS Speech Cherry Hill N.J. 5/7/74, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - "Nonferrous Bargaining Structures - Unions&; Companies" Romey Meeting 3-23-77, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - BR- Annual Report on LMC NYC 6/17/74, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - American Arbitration Ass. DS Speech (Cancelled) 10/10/74, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - IHF Pittsburgh 10-23-74, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Graphic Arts of Union Employees of America 11-9-1974 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Georgia State U 12-5-74 & FMCS, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - IRRA Panel San Francisco 12-27-74, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - DS Interview - Iron Age 9-8-75, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - DS Speech- Washington, D.C. November 17,1975 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Industrial College of the Armed Forces D.C. Nov. 19, 1975, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - MIT Speech - Sloan Fellow Talk December, 10, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Hawaii March 6, 1967 March 9, 1967 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Hawaii March 6, 1967 March 9, 1967 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Soutar Speeches. (Box 19)
  - ASPA - Overview of Bargaining for 1976: 2/12/76 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Romney Meeting - April, 1976 "Overview of Bargaining. For 1976" (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Waldorf - 1975 10-15-75 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - DS Speech- Executive Enterprises 2/19/81 Arlington, Va. (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - DS Speech- Executive Enterprises 2/19/81 Arlington, Va. (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - DS Speech - March 11, 1981 Wash DC Pepper, Hamilton & Scheetz (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Executive Enterprises Arlington, Va Feb. 19-20, 1981 (Folder 1 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Executive Enterprises Arlington, Va Feb. 19-20, 1981 (Folder 2 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Executive Enterprises Arlington, Va Feb. 19-20, 1981 (Folder 3 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 9)